Photon Satellite Descrição: [Machine/Effect] You can target 1 face-up "Photon" monster you control; increase this card's Level by that target's Level. If this card is used as an Xyz Material for an Xyz Summon, you can treat it as 2 monsters.

Kuriphoton Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] During either player's turn: You can send this card from your hand to the Graveyard and pay half your Life Points; you take no damage until the End Phase. If this card is in your Graveyard: You can send 1 "Photon" monster from your hand to the Graveyard; add this card to your hand.

Milus Radiant Descrição: [Beast/Effect] As long as this card remains face-up on the field, increase the ATK of all EARTH monsters by 500 points and decrease the ATK of all WIND monsters by 400 points.

Sinister Sprocket Descrição: [Fiend/Tuner] If this card is sent to the Graveyard for the Synchro Summon of a DARK Synchro Monster, you can destroy 1 face-up Spell or Trap Card.

Treeborn Frog Descrição: [Aqua/Effect] During your Standby Phase, if this card is in your Graveyard and you do not control a "Treeborn Frog": You can Special Summon this card. You must control no Spell/Trap Cards to activate and to resolve this effect.

Bee List Soldier Decrição: [Insect/Effect] You can Tribute this card and 1 face-up Insect-Type monster, except "Bee List Soldier", to draw 2 cards.

Oppressed People Decrição: [Aqua] They are oppressed, but believe they will have their freedom someday.

Stoic of Prophecy Descrição: [Spellcaster/Effect] When this card is sent to the Graveyard: Add 1 Level 3 "Prophecy" monster from your Deck to your hand.

Volcanic Shell Descrição: [Pyro/Effect] Once per turn: You can pay 500 Life Points; add 1 "Volcanic Shell" from your Deck to your hand. This card must be in the Graveyard to activate and to resolve this effect.

Kuriboo (HQ) Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] You can discard 1 Trap Card to select 1 face-up monster your opponent controls. That monster loses 1500 ATK until the End Phase. This card cannot be Tributed for a Tribute Summon.

Kuribee (HQ) Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] When a face-up "Kuribah", "Kuribeh", "Kuribee", "Kuriboh" or "Kuriboo" you control is selected as an attack target, you can negate that attack. This card cannot be Tributed for a Tribute Summon.

Kuribeh (HQ) Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] You can remove from play 1 "Kuribah", "Kuribee", "Kuriboh", "Kuriboo" and this card you control to Special Summon 1 "Kuribandit" from your hand or Deck. This card cannot be Tributed for a Tribute Summon.

Kuribah (HQ) Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] You can remove from play 1 "Kuribeh", "Kuribee", "Kuriboh", "Kuriboo", and this card you control to Special Summon 1 "Kuribabylon" from your hand, Deck, or Graveyard. This card cannot be Tributed for a Tribute Summon.

Jester Confit Descrição: [Spellcaster/Effect] You can Special Summon this card from your hand in face-up Attack Position. If you do, return this card and 1 face-up monster your opponent controls to the hand during the End Phase of your opponent's next turn. You can only control 1 face-up "Jester Confit".

D.D. Crow Descrição: [Winged Beast/Effect] During either player's turn: You can discard this card to the Graveyard to target 1 card in your opponent's Graveyard; banish that target.

D.D. Trainer Descrição: [Fiend] A poor goblin that was sucked into a different dimension. However, he's doing his best with his new destiny.

Swordsman from a Foreign Land Descrição: [Warrior/Effect] A monster attacked by this card will be destroyed during the End Phase of the 5th turn after the attack.

Wisel Top Descrição: [Machine/Effect] If you do not control a face-up "Meklord Emperor" monster, destroy this card.

Wisel Guard Descrição: [Machine/Effect] If you do not control a face-up "Meklord Emperor" monster, destroy this card. When another monster you control is selected as an attack target, you can switch the target to this card instead.

Wisel Carrier Descrição: [Machine/Effect] Destroy this card if you do not control a "Meklord Emperor" monster. This card cannot be destroyed by your opponent's card effects.

Wisel Attack Descrição: [Machine/Effect] If you do not control a face-up "Meklord Emperor" monster, destroy this card.

Wise Core Descrição: [Machine/Effect] When this card is destroyed by a card effect and sent to the Graveyard, destroy all monsters you control. Then, Special Summon 1 "Meklord Emperor Wisel", "Wisel Top", "Wisel Attack", "Wisel Guard", and "Wisel Carrier" from your hand, Deck, or Graveyard.

Fortune Fairy Hikari Descrição: [Spellcaster] Your fortune the day you draw this card is super happy. Lucky number, 1 Lucky color, yellow. Lucky item, shining charm. All of your wishes will come true!!

T.G. Gear Zombie Descrição: [Zombie/Tuner] You can have 1 face-up Machine-Type monster lose 1000 ATK: Special Summon this card from your hand. This card can also be treated as a Machine-Type monster. When a Spell/Trap Card you control targets this card: You can halve this card's original ATK and DEF. When this card is destroyed: You can add 1 "T.G." monster from your Deck to your hand. You cannot Summon it this turn.

Unknown Synchron Descrição: [Machine/Tuner] If your opponent controls a monster and you control no monsters, you can Special Summon this card from your hand.

Blackwing - Jin the Rain Shadow Descrição: [Winged Beast/Tuner] If this card battles with a monster with DEF equal to or less than this card's ATK, destroy that monster immediately with this card's effect (without applying damage calculation).

Crimson Ninja Descrição: [Warrior/Effect] FLIP: Target 1 Trap Card on the field; destroy that target. (If the target is Set, reveal it, and destroy it if it is a Trap Card. Otherwise, return it to its original position.)

Armed Ninja Descrição: [Warrior/Effect] FLIP: Target 1 Spell Card on the field; destroy that target. (If the target is Set, reveal it, and destroy it if it is a Spell Card. Otherwise, return it to its original position.)

Tuningware Descrição: [Machine/Effect] If this card is used for a Synchro Summon, you can treat it as a Level 2 monster. If this card is sent to the Graveyard for a Synchro Summon: Draw 1 card.

Stardust Xiaolong Descrição: [Dragon/Effect] If this card is in your Graveyard while you control a face-up "Stardust Dragon", you can Special Summon it. Once per turn, if this card would be destroyed by battle, it is not destroyed.

Level Eater Descrição: [Insect/Effect] If this card is in the Graveyard: You can target 1 face-up Level 5 or higher monster you control; reduce its Level by 1, and if you do, Special Summon this card from the Graveyard. This card cannot be Tributed except for a Tribute Summon.

Dverg of the Nordic Alfar Descrição: [Warrior/Effect] During the turn this card is Normal Summoned, you can Normal Summon 1 "Nordic" monster in addition to your Normal Summon or Set. (You can only gain this effect once per turn.) When this face-up card on the field is sent to the Graveyard, select 1 "Nordic Relic" card in your Graveyard and add it to your hand.

Supay Descrição: [Fiend/Tuner] When this card is sent from the field to the Graveyard by a card effect, you can Special Summon 1 "Oracle of the Sun" from your Deck. The ATK of that monster is doubled, and it returns to the owner's hand during the End Phase of that turn.

Copy Plant Descrição: [Plant/Tuner] Once per turn, you can select 1 face-up monster on the field to have this card's Level become equal to the selected monster's Level, until the End Phase.

Morphtronic Magnen Bar Descrição: [Thunder/Effect] ● While in Attack Position: Once per turn, if you control exactly 2 other face-up Attack Position monsters, and no additional monsters, this card gains the combined ATK of the other two monsters you control until the End Phase. The other two monsters cannot attack the turn you activate this effect. ● While in Defense Position: Monsters you control cannot attack.

Acorno Descrição: [Plant/Effect] During your Main Phase: You can send 1 "Pinecono" from your hand to the Graveyard, and Special Summon this card from the hand.

Abyss Boat Watchman Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] When this card is destroyed and sent to the Graveyard, inflict 800 damage to your opponent. If you controlled this card when it was destroyed and sent to the Graveyard, then while this card is in the Graveyard, when an opponent's monster declares an attack, you can select 1 "Abyss" monster in your Graveyard, and Special Summon it.

Evil Thorn Descrição: [Plant/Effect] You can Tribute this card to inflict 300 damage to your opponent and Special Summon up to 2 "Evil Thorn"(s) from your Deck in face-up Attack Position. Those monsters' effects cannot be activated.

Dark Spider Descrição: [Insect/Effect] Once per turn, you can increase the Level of 1 face-up Insect-Type monster you control by 2, until the End Phase.

Dark Bug Descrição: [Insect/Effect] When this card is Normal Summoned successfully, you can Special Summon 1 Level 3 Tuner monster from your Graveyard.

Cyber Valley Descrição: [Machine/Effect] Select and activate 1 of the following effects. ● Activate only during the Battle Phase. Remove this card from play. End the Battle Phase and draw 1 card. You can activate this effect during either player’s turn. ● Remove from play this card and 1 card you control to draw 2 cards. ● Remove from play this card and 1 card in your hand to select 1 card in your Graveyard and add it to your hand. It cannot be activated or Summoned this turn.

Majestic Dragon Descrição: [Dragon/Tuner] This card cannot be used as a Synchro Material Monster, except for the Synchro Summon of a "Majestic" monster.

Alien Ammonite Descrição: [Reptile/Tuner] When this card is Normal Summoned, you can Special Summon 1 Level 4 or lower "Alien" monster from your Graveyard. Destroy it during the End Phase.

Red-Eyes B. Chick Descrição: [Dragon/Effect] You can send this face-up card to the Graveyard; Special Summon 1 "Red-Eyes B. Dragon" from your hand.

Infernity Zero Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] This card cannot be Normal Summoned or Set. This card cannot be Special Summoned except by this card's effect. If your Life Points would become 0 by effect damage, you can Special Summon this card by discarding all other cards in your hand. While you control this face-up card, you cannot lose the Duel. This card cannot be destroyed by battle. Each time you take damage, place 1 Doom Counter on this card (max. 3) for each multiple of 500 damage you take. When there are 3 Doom Counters on this card, destroy this card.

Infernity Mirage Descrição:[Fiend/Effect] During either player's turn, if you have no cards in your hand, you can Tribute this card to Special Summon 2 "Infernity" monsters from your Graveyard, except "Infernity Mirage".

Infernity Des Gunman Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] If you have no cards in your hand when your opponent activates an effect that would inflict damage, you can remove from play this card from your Graveyard to activate this effect. Draw 1 card and reveal it. If it is a Monster Card, your opponent takes damage equal to the amount of effect damage you took this turn, and all effect damage you would take this turn is inflicted to your opponent instead. Otherwise, take damage equal to the amount of effect damage you took this turn. Your opponent can negate this card's effect, but you take no effect damage this turn.

Infernity Avenger Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] When a monster you control, except "Infernity Avenger", is destroyed by battle with an opponent's monster and sent to the Graveyard, while you have no cards in your hand, you can Special Summon this card from your Graveyard. In that case, the Level of this card is equal to the Level of your destroyed monster.

Monster Eye Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] You can pay 1000 Life Points; add 1 "Polymerization" from your Graveyard to your hand.

Charcoal Inpachi Descrição: [Pyro] A wicked wooden spirit that has burned out. The barbecue grilled with this charcoal is so awesome that everybody thinks it's priceless.

Charm of Shabti Descrição: [Rock/Effect] During either player's turn: You can discard this card; until the End Phase, "Gravekeeper's" monsters you control cannot be destroyed by battle.

Magician of Faith Descrição: [Spellcaster/Effect] FLIP: Add 1 Spell Card from your Graveyard to your hand.

Horus' Servant Descrição: [Beast-Warrior/Effect] Your opponent cannot target face-up "Horus the Black Flame Dragon" monsters with Spells, Traps, or card effects.

Ceruli, Guru of Dark World Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] If this card is discarded to the Graveyard by a card effect: Special Summon this card from the Graveyard to your opponent's side of the field in face-up Defense Position. When this card is Special Summoned by the effect of a "Dark World" card: Your opponent must discard 1 card.

Thousand-Eyes Restrict Descrição: [Spellcaster/Fusion/Effect] "Relinquished" + "Thousand-Eyes Idol" Other monsters cannot change their battle position or attack. Once per turn, you can equip 1 monster your opponent controls to this card (max 1). This card's ATK and DEF become the same as the equipped monster's. If this card would be destroyed by battle, the equipped monster is destroyed instead.

Thousand-Eyes Idol Descrição: [Spellcaster] A wicked entity that controls the hearts of men, its thousand eyes are able to see and expand the negative influences in an individual's soul.

Relinquished Descrição: [Spellcaster/Ritual/Effect] You can Ritual Summon this card with "Black Illusion Ritual". Once per turn: You can target 1 monster your opponent controls; equip that target to this card. (You can only equip 1 monster at a time to this card with this effect.) This card's ATK and DEF become equal to that equipped monster's. If this card would be destroyed by battle, destroy that equipped monster instead. While equipped with that monster, any battle damage you take from battles involving this card inflicts equal effect damage to your opponent.

Kuriboh Descrição: [Fiend/Effect] During your opponent's turn, at damage calculation: You can discard this card; you take no Battle Damage from that battle.

Copycat Descrição: [Spellcaster/Effect] When this card is Summoned: Target 1 face-up monster your opponent controls; this card's ATK and DEF become equal to that monster's original ATK and DEF.

Winged Kuriboh Descrição: [Fairy/Effect] If this card on the field is destroyed and sent to the Graveyard: Any further Battle Damage you take this turn becomes 0.
