Obelisk the Tormentor Descrição: [Divine-Beast/Effect] Requires 3 Tributes to Normal Summon (cannot be Normal Set). 
This card's Normal Summon cannot be negated. When Normal Summoned, Spells, Traps, Spell/Trap effects, and the effects of non-DIVINE monsters cannot be activated. 
While face-up on the field, this card is also Warrior-Type. Your opponent cannot Tribute this card. Control of this card cannot switch. 
Cannot be targeted by, or leave the field by, the effects of Spell/Trap Cards and non-DIVINE monsters, except by its own effect. 
Other card effects are only applied on this card until the End Phase. This effect cannot be negated. 
During the End Phase, if this card was Special Summoned: Send it to the Graveyard. If this card is Special Summoned in face-up Defense Position when an opponent's monster declares an attack, OR if exactly 1 monster you control is targeted by a card effect that could of targeted this card, that attack or card effect now targets this card, instead. 
During either player's turn: You can Tribute 2 monsters; apply 1 of these effects. 
* Destroy all monsters your opponent controls, and inflict 4000 damage to your opponent. This card cannot declare an attack the turn this effect is activated. 
* This card's ATK becomes ∞ (Infinity) until the End Phase.