The Winged Dragon of Ra (draft) Anime 1st Version Anime 2nd Version Descrição: [Divine-Beast/Effect] This card cannot be Normal Summoned except by Tributing 3 monsters (you cannot Set this card). 
The Normal Summon of this card cannot be negated. When this card is Normal Summoned, Spells/Trap Cards, and other card effects except its own cannot be activated. 
If this card is Tribute Summoned, its original ATK and DEF become the total respective ATK and DEF of the Tributed monsters. 
You can change the Battle Position of this card during the turn you Normal Summoned this card. 
While face-up on the field, this card is unaffected by other card effects, including the effects of "Obelisk the Tormentor" and "Slifer the Sky Dragon:. If this card is Special Summoned from the Graveyard: 
*This card can attack all monsters your opponent controls once each. If your opponent controls no monsters after this effect resolves, it can attack your opponent directly, even if it has already attacked one or more times this turn. 
*If Summoned in face-up Defense Position when a monster your opponent controls declares an attack, you can change the attack target to this card. 
*It is sent to the Graveyard during the End Phase. The following effects may be activated at any time of the duel: 
*Pay all but 1 of your Life Points to increase this card’s ATK and DEF by the total Life Points you paid. You can also Tribute all other monsters you control to increase this card’s ATK by the total ATK of the Tributed monsters. 
*By discarding 1 “De-Fusion” during your turn, or sending it face-down to the Graveyard; gain Life Points equal to this card’s ATK, then decrease its ATK and DEF by the total Life Points you gained. If you use this effect when this card declares an attack, negate that attack. 
*Pay 1000 Life Points to destroy one monster your opponent controls(negating any effects which would prevent it being destroyed) except during the Battle Phase.

