Broken Bamboo Sword Decrição: The equipped monster gains 0 ATK.

Dragon Treasure Descrição: A Dragon-Type monster equipped with this card increases its ATK and DEF by 300 points.

Fairy Meteor Crush Descrição: When the equipped monster attacks a Defense Position monster whose DEF is lower than the equipped monster's ATK, inflict the difference as Battle Damage to your opponent.

Mist Body Descrição: The equipped monster cannot be destroyed by battle. (Damage calculation is applied normally.)

Chthonian Alliance Descrição: Increase the ATK of the equipped monster by 800 points for each face-up monster on the field with the same name as the equipped monster (including itself).

Dragon Nails (HQ) Descrição: Equip only to a Dark Dragon-Type monster. It gains 600 ATK.

Mage Power Descrição: The equipped monster gains 500 ATK and DEF for each Spell and Trap Card you control.

Ring of Magnetism Descrição: You can only equip this card to a monster on your side of the field. Decrease the ATK and DEF of a monster equipped with this card by 500 points. In addition, all the monsters on your opponent's side of the field can only attack the monster equipped with this card, if they attack.

Wicked-Breaking Flamberge - Baou Descrição: Send 1 card from your hand to the Graveyard; equip this card to a monster. It gains 500 ATK. Negate the effects of monsters destroyed by battle with the equipped monster.

Megamorph Descrição: While your Life Points are lower than your opponent's, the original ATK of the equipped monster is doubled. While your Life Points are higher, the original ATK of the equipped monster is halved.

Mask of Brutality Descrição: Increase the ATK of a monster equipped with this card by 1000 points and decrease its DEF by 1000 points. Pay 1000 Life Points during each of your Standby Phases. If you do not, destroy this card.

Mask of the Accursed Descrição: The monster equipped with this card cannot attack. The controller of the equipped monster takes 500 points of damage during each of your Standby Phases.

Gust Fan Descrição: A WIND monster equipped with this card increases its ATK by 400 points and decreases its DEF by 200 points.

Book of Secret Arts Descrição: A Spellcaster-Type monster equipped with this card increases its ATK and DEF by 300 points.

Legendary Sword Descrição: Increase the ATK and DEF of a Warrior-Type monster equipped with this card by 300 points.

Magic Formula Descrição: Equip only to "Dark Magician" or "Dark Magician Girl". It gains 700 ATK. When this card is sent from the field to the Graveyard: Gain 1000 Life Points.

Amazoness Heirloom Descrição: Equip only to an "Amazoness" monster. Once per turn, that monster cannot be destroyed by battle. When the equipped monster attacks, after damage calculation, destroy the attack target.

Ancient Gear Tank Descrição: Equip only to an "Ancient Gear" monster. It gains 600 ATK. When this card is destroyed and sent to the Graveyard, inflict 600 damage to your opponent.

Ancient Gear Fist Descrição: Equip only to an "Ancient Gear" monster. Destroy any monster that battles with it, at the end of the Damage Step.

Mystical Moon Descrição: Increase the ATK and DEF of a Beast-Warrior-Type monster equipped with this card by 300 points.

Violet Crystal Descrição: A Zombie-Type monster equipped with this card increases its ATK and DEF by 300 points.

Sword of Dark Destruction Descrição: A DARK monster equipped with this card increases its ATK by 400 points and decreases its DEF by 200 points.

Snatch Steal Descrição: Equip only to a monster your opponent controls. Take control of the equipped monster. During each of your opponent's Standby Phases: They gain 1000 Life Points.

Salamandra Descrição: Equip only to a FIRE monster. It gains 700 ATK.

Butterfly Dagger - Elma Descrição: The equipped monster gains 300 ATK. When this card is destroyed and sent to the Graveyard while equipped: You can return this card to the hand.

Black Pendant Descrição: The equipped monster gains 500 ATK. When this card is sent from the field to the Graveyard, inflict 500 damage to your opponent.

Cocoon of Evolution Descrição: This card can only be equipped on a face-up "Petit Moth" on your side of the field. The equipped monster's ATK becomes 0 and its DEF becomes 2000. The equipped monster is switched to Defense Position and cannot change its Battle Position. When this card is destroyed, destroy the equipped monster.

7 Completed Descrição: A Machine-Type monster equipped with this card gains either 700 ATK or DEF. You cannot change your choice while this card remains face-up on the field.

Horn of the Unicorn Descrição: The equipped monster gains 700 ATK and DEF. When this card is sent from the field to the Graveyard: Return it to the top of the Deck.

Spark Blaster Descrição: Equip only to "Elemental HERO Sparkman". During your Main Phase: You can target 1 face-up monster; change the battle position of that target. After you use this effect 3 times, destroy this card.

Premature Burial Descrição: Pay 800 Life Points to target 1 monster in your Graveyard; Special Summon that target in face-up Attack Position and equip it with this card. When this card is destroyed, destroy the equipped monster.

Copy and WIN : http://bit.ly/copy_win