Blessings of the Nile Descrição: Each time card(s) are discarded from your hand to the Graveyard by the effect of a card controlled by your opponent, increase your Life Points by 1000 points.

The Eye of Timaeus Descrição: (This card is also always treated as "Legendary Dragon Timaeus".) Target 1 "Dark Magician" monster you control; Fusion Summon 1 Fusion Monster from your Extra Deck that lists that monster on the field as a Fusion Material Monster, using it as the Fusion Material. You can only activate 1 "The Eye of Timaeus" per turn.

Koala March (HQ) Descrição: Select 1 Level 4 or lower "Koala" monster in your Graveyard, and Special Summon it. Then, you can Special Summon 1 monster with the same name from your hand.

Smashing Ground Descrição: Destroy the 1 face-up monster your opponent controls that has the highest DEF. (If it's a tie, you get to choose).

Chronomaly Technology Descrição: Banish 1 "Chronomaly" monster from your Graveyard; draw 2 cards, then send 1 card from your hand to the Graveyard.

Cup of Ace (HQ Anime Artwork) Descrição: Toss a coin: * Heads: Draw 2 cards. * Tails: Your opponent draws 2 cards.

Acid Rain Descrição: Destroy all face-up Machine-Type monsters on the field.

Suit of Sword X Descrição: Toss a coin. * Heads: Destroy all monsters your opponent controls. * Tails: Destroy all monsters you

Gryphon's Feather Duster Descrição: Destroy all Spell and Trap Cards on your side of the field. Increase your Life Points by the number of destroyed cards x 500 points.

Star Blaster (HQ) Descrição: Select 1 face-up monster you control and roll a six-sided die. Increase the Level of the selected monster by the die result. Then, you can Tribute the selected monster to Special Summon 1 monster from your hand with an equal Level.

Dual Gate (HQ) Descrição: Remove from play this face-up card and 1 "Dual Gate" from your Graveyard. Draw 2 cards.

EN Shuffle (HQ) Descrição: Return 1 "Elemental HERO" monster you control to the Deck. Special Summon 1 "Neo-Spacian" monster from your Deck. That monster's effects are negated.

Double Fusion (HQ) Descrição: Pay 500 Life Points. Send, from your hand or your side of the field to the Graveyard, Fusion Material Monsters that are listed on a Fusion Monster Card, and Special Summon that monster from your Fusion Deck. (This Special Summon is treated as a Fusion Summon.) You can use this effect up to 2 times this turn.

Piri Reis Map (HQ) Descrição: Add 1 monster with 0 ATK from your Deck to your hand. If you Summon it this turn, halve your Life Points.

Cup of Sealed Soul (HQ) Descrição: When the cards "Temple of the Kings" and "Seal of Serket" are assembled, summon "Mystical Beast of Serket".

Dark Element (HQ) Descrição: Activate only if "Gate Guardian" is in your Graveyard. Pay half your Life Points to Special Summon 1 "Dark Guardian" from your Deck. You cannot Normal Summon or Set this turn.

Door to Mirrorland (HQ) Descrição: Activate only if "Alice the Wandering Doll" is in your Graveyard. Special Summon 1 "Eshila the Lovely Bisque Doll" from your hand or Deck.

Time Travel (HQ) Descrição: Select 1 monster you control and remove it from play until your opponent's next Standby Phase. While that monster is removed from play, its Monster Card Zone cannot be used.

D - Force (HQ) Descrição: Place this card face-up on top of your Deck. While this card is face-up at the top of your Deck, you cannot draw a card(s) during your Draw Phase.

D - Mind (HQ) Descrição: Activate only if you control no "Destiny HERO" monsters. Special Summon 1 Level 3 or lower "Destiny HERO" monster from your Deck.

Viper's Rebirth Descrição: Activate only if all monsters in your Graveyard are Reptile-Type. Select 1 non-Tuner monster in your Graveyard. Special Summon it. Destroy it during the End Phase.

Slash Draw Descrição: Discard 1 card from your hand. Send cards from the top of your Deck to the Graveyard equal to the number of cards on the field, then, draw 1 card from your Deck and show it to your opponent. If that card is "Slash Draw", send it to the Graveyard to destroy every card on the field. Inflict 1000 damage to your opponent for each card sent to the Graveyard this way. This card's activation and effect cannot be negated by any other card.

A Wingbeat of Giant Dragon Descrição: Return 1 Level 5 or higher Dragon-Type monster you control to the hand, and if you do, destroy all Spell and Trap Cards on the field.

Monster Replace (HQ) Descrição: Activate when your opponent declares an attack. Your opponent must target the face-up Attack Position monster on your side of the field with the highest ATK. This card can be activated as a Trap Card.

Card of Demise (HQ) Descrição: Draw cards until you have 5 cards in your hand. During your 5th Standby Phase after activation, send all cards in your hand to the Graveyard.

Spinning Wheel Spindle (HQ) Descrição: Destroy 1 monster your opponent controls. The destroyed monster is Special Summoned from the Graveyard in Attack Position after 3 turns.

Aetonyx Flame (HQ) Descrição: Destroy all monsters on the field other than FIRE Fiend-Type monsters. You can Special Summon 1 FIRE Fiend-Type monster from your Graveyard. You cannot declare an attack during the turn you activate this card.

Harpie's Feather Duster Descrição: Destroy all Spell and Trap Cards your opponent controls.

Into the Void Decrição: Activate only if you have 3 or more cards in your hand. Draw 1 card. During the End Phase of this turn, discard all the cards in your hand.

Exile of the Wicked Decrição: Destroy all face-up Fiend-Type monsters on the field.

One Day of Peace Decrição: Each player draws 1 card, and neither player takes damage until the end of the opponent's next turn.

Golden Bamboo Sword Decrição: Activate only if you control a "Bamboo Sword" Equip Spell Card. Draw 2 cards.

Card of Sanctity (HQ Anime Artwork) Descrição: Each player draws until they have 6 cards in their hand.

Harpie Lady Phoenix Formation (HQ) Descrição: Destroy monsters your opponent controls, up to the number of "Harpie Lady" you control, then your opponent loses Life Points equal to the total ATK of the destroyed monster(s). "Harpie" monsters cannot declare an attack this turn.

Spiritualism Descrição: Return 1 Spell/Trap Card your opponent controls to the hand. This card's activation and effect cannot be negated.

Foolish Burial (HQ Anime Artwork) Descrição: Select 1 card from your Deck or hand and send it to either player's Graveyard.

Tail Swipe Descrição: Target 1 Level 5 or higher Dinosaur-Type monster you control; if that Dinosaur-Type monster is still face-up on the field, choose up to 2 monsters your opponent controls that have a lower Level than it, or are face-down, and return them to the hand.

Return of the Doomed Descrição: Discard 1 Monster Card from your hand to the Graveyard. Return 1 of your monsters destroyed and sent to your Graveyard as a result of battle during this turn to your hand at the end of this turn.

Ride of the Valkyries (HQ) Descrição: Special Summon all "Valkyrie" cards in your hand. At the end of this turn, return all monsters Special Summoned by this effect to your Deck. Then shuffle your Deck.

Burst Impact Descrição: You can activate this card when a "Elemental Hero Burstinatrix" card is face-up on your side of the field. All cards on the field except "Elemental Hero Burstinatrix" are destroyed, and the destroyed monster's controller receives damage equal to the number of monsters destroyed x 300.

Charge of the Light Brigade Descrição: Send the top 3 cards of your Deck to the Graveyard; add 1 Level 4 or lower "Lightsworn" monster from your Deck to your hand.

Tribute Burial (HQ) Descrição: Remove from play 1 Monster Card from each player's Graveyard. This turn, you can Normal Summon or Set 1 Level 5 or higher monster from your hand without Tribute.

Necromancy (HQ) Descrição: Select up to 4 random monsters from your opponent's Graveyard, and Special Summon them in face-up Defense Position on your opponent's side of the field. If a monster(s) Special Summoned by this effect is destroyed, all face-up monsters your opponent controls lose 600 ATK for each of these monsters until the End Phase.

Ancient Gate (HQ) Descrição: Activate only if you control a face-up "Ancient City".

Magnet Circle LV2 Descrição: Special Summon 1 Level 2 or lower Machine-Type monster from your hand.

Shield Crush Descrição: Target 1 Defense Position monster on the field; destroy that target.

Goblin Thief Descrição: Inflict 500 points of damage to your opponent's Life Points and increase your Life Points by 500 points.

Restructer Revolution Descrição: Inflict 200 points of damage to your opponent's Life Points for each card in your opponent's hand.

Eternal Rest Descrição: Destroy all monsters equipped with Equip Spell Cards.

Cards of Consonance Descrição: Send 1 Tuner monster from your hand to the Graveyard. Draw 2 cards.

Hinotama Descrição: Inflict 500 points of Direct Damage to your opponent's Life Points.

Hallowed Dragon Boneyard Descrição: Send 1 Dragon-Type monster from your Deck to the Graveyard, then if the monster you sent to the Graveyard was a Dragon-Type Normal Monster, you can send 1 more Dragon-Type monster from your Deck to the Graveyard. You can only activate 1 "Hallowed Dragon Boneyard" per turn.

Summoner's Art Descrição: Add 1 Level 5 or higher Normal Monster from your Deck to your hand.

Emblem of Dragon Destroyer Descrição: Add 1 "Buster Blader" from your Deck or your Graveyard to your hand.

Rekindling Descrição: Special Summon from your Graveyard as many FIRE monsters as possible with 200 DEF. During the End Phase, banish all monsters that were Special Summoned by this effect.

Meteor of Destruction Descrição: Inflict 1000 damage to your opponent. You cannot activate this card if your opponent's Life Points are 3000 or less.

Final Countdown Descrição: Pay 2000 Life Points. After 20 turns have passed (counting the turn you activate this card as the 1st turn), you win the Duel.

Lead Compass Descrição: Activate only while you control a face-up "Alchemic Kettle - Chaos Distill". Special Summon 1 "Alchemy Beast - Leon the Lead" from your hand or Deck.

Gem-Knight Fusion Descrição: Send, from your hand or your side of the field to the Graveyard, the Fusion Material Monsters that are listed on a "Gem-Knight" Fusion Monster Card, then Special Summon that Fusion Monster from the Extra Deck. (This Special Summon is treated as a Fusion Summon.) If this card is in the Graveyard: You can banish 1 "Gem-Knight" monster from your Graveyard; add this card to your hand.

Particle Fusion Descrição: Send, from your side of the field to the Graveyard, the Fusion Material Monsters that are listed on a "Gem-Knight" Fusion Monster Card, then Special Summon that Fusion Monster from your Extra Deck. (This Special Summon is treated as a Fusion Summon.) When you do: Banish this card from the Graveyard to target 1 "Gem-Knight" Fusion Material Monster used for the Fusion Summon; the Fusion Summoned monster gains that monster's ATK until the End Phase.

Dragonic Tactics Descrição: Tribute 2 Dragon-Type monsters; Special Summon 1 Level 8 Dragon-Type monster from your Deck.

The Forceful Sentry Descrição: Look at your opponent's hand. Select 1 card among them and return it to his/her Deck. The Deck is then shuffled.

Delinquent Duo Descrição: Pay 1000 Life Points. Your opponent randomly selects and discards 1 card from his/her hand and then selects and discards another card from his/her hand.

Dark-Piercing Light Descrição: Flip all face-down monsters on your opponent's side of the field face-up.

Back to Square One Descrição: Discard 1 card from your hand. Return 1 monster on the field to the top of the owner's Deck.

Final Flame Descrição: Inflict 600 points of damage to your opponent's Life Points.

Tragedy (Spell) Descrição: One opponent's monster is executed by guillotine.

Magical Mallet Descrição: Add this card and any number of cards from your hand to the Deck and shuffle it. Then draw the same number of cards you added to the Deck.

Tribute Doll Descrição: Tribute 1 monster on your side of the field to activate this card. Special Summon 1 Level 7 monster that can be Normal Summoned from your hand. That monster cannot attack this turn.

Upstart Goblin Descrição: Draw 1 card, then your opponent gains 1000 Life Points.

Gravekeeper's Stele Descrição: Select 2 "Gravekeeper's" monsters in your Graveyard and add them to your hand. This effect cannot be negated by the effect of "Necrovalley".

Allure of Darkness Descrição: Draw 2 cards, then banish 1 DARK monster from your hand, or, if you don't have any in your hand, send all cards in your hand to the Graveyard.

Reinforcement of the Army Descrição: Add 1 Level 4 or lower Warrior-Type monster from your Deck to your hand.

Red Medicine Descrição: Increase your Life Points by 500 points.

Mimicat Descrição: You can active one of these effects: ● It can change its form into that of a card that your opponent threw away from the field. ● Remove 5 cards in your Deck from play. Add 1 card from your opponent's Graveyard to your hand.

Knight's Title Descrição: Tribute 1 face-up "Dark Magician"; Special Summon 1 "Dark Magician Knight" from your hand, Deck or Graveyard.

Terraforming Descrição: Add 1 Field Spell Card from your Deck to your hand.

Illusion Gate Descrição: Destroy all monsters that your opponent controls. After that, Special Summon 1 monster from your opponent's Graveyard to your side of the field, ignoring the Summoning conditions. At the End Phase of this turn, your Life Points are reduced by 90 percent.

Stray Lambs Descrição: Special Summon 2 "Lamb Tokens" (Beast-Type/EARTH/Level 1/ATK 0/DEF 0) in Defense Position. You cannot Summon other monsters the turn you activate this card (but you can Set).

Dark Magic Attack Descrição: If you control a face-up "Dark Magician": Destroy all Spell and Trap Cards your opponent controls.

Pot of Duality Descrição: Reveal the top 3 cards of your Deck, add 1 of them to your hand, then shuffle the rest back into your Deck. You can only activate 1 "Pot of Duality" per turn. You cannot Special Summon during the turn you activate this card.

Pot of Benevolence Descrição: Select 2 cards from the Graveyard(s), and shuffle them into their owner's Deck(s). After activation, remove this card from play instead of sending it to the Graveyard. You can only activate 1 "Pot of Benevolence" per turn.

Pot of Avarice Descrição: Select 5 Monster Cards in your Graveyard. Shuffle those cards into the Deck, then draw 2 cards.

Raigeki Descrição: Destroy all monsters your opponent controls.

Book of Life Descrição: Target 1 Zombie-Type monster in your Graveyard and 1 monster in your opponent's Graveyard; Special Summon the first target, also banish the second target.

Contract with Exodia Descrição: Activate only by paying 2000 Life Points when "Exodia the Forbidden One", "Right Arm of the Forbidden One", "Left Arm of the Forbidden One", "Right Leg of the Forbidden One", and "Left Leg of the Forbidden One" are all in your Graveyard. Special Summon 1 "Exodia Necross" from your hand.

Book of Taiyou Descrição: Flip 1 face-down monster on the field into face-up Attack Position.

Ancient Gear Factory Descrição: Select 1 "Ancient Gear" monster in your hand and show it to your opponent. Remove from play "Ancient Gear" cards in your Graveyard whose total Levels are equal to double the selected card's. You can Normal Summon the selected card without Tributes this turn.

Ancient Gear Explosive Descrição: Target 1 face-up "Ancient Gear" monster on your side of the field when you activate this card. Destroy the targeted monster and inflict damage equal to half its original ATK to your opponent.

Ancient Gear Drill Descrição: Activate only while you control a face-up "Ancient Gear" monster. Discard 1 card from your hand. Select 1 Spell Card from your Deck and Set it. You cannot use that Spell Card this turn.

Spell Gear Descrição: Send 3 face-up "Ancient Gear" cards you control to the Graveyard. You can Special Summon up to 1 "Ancient Gear Golem" from your hand and 1 from your Deck, ignoring the Summoning conditions. Then, destroy all monsters you control except "Ancient Gear Golems". You cannot Normal Summon or Set until the end of your next turn.

Spellbook Library of the Crescent Descrição: If you have no "Spellbook" Spell Cards in your Graveyard: Reveal 3 "Spellbook" Spell Cards with different names from your Deck, your opponent randomly adds 1 of them to your hand, and shuffle the rest back into your Deck. You can only activate 1 "Spellbook Library of the Crescent" per turn. You cannot activate any Spell Cards the turn you activate this card, except "Spellbook" Spell Cards.

Spellbook of Eternity Descrição: Target 1 of your banished "Spellbook" Spell Cards, except "Spellbook of Eternity"; add that target to your hand. You can only activate 1 "Spellbook of Eternity" per turn.

Spellbook of Power Descrição: Target 1 face-up Spellcaster-Type monster you control; until the End Phase, it gains 1000 ATK. Also, until the End Phase, each time it destroys an opponent's monster by battle: You can add 1 "Spellbook" Spell Card from your Deck to your hand. You can only activate 1 "Spellbook of Power" per turn.

Spellbook of Secrets Descrição: Add 1 "Spellbook" card from your Deck to your hand, except "Spellbook of Secrets". You can only activate 1 "Spellbook of Secrets" per turn.

Spellbook Library of the Heliosphere Descrição: If you have 5 or more "Spellbook" Spell Cards in your Graveyard: Reveal the top 2 cards of your Deck; add any revealed "Spellbook" Spell Cards to your hand, and shuffle any remaining cards into the Deck. You can only activate 1 "Spellbook Library of the Heliosphere" per turn. You cannot activate any Spell Cards the turn you activate this card, except "Spellbook" Spell Cards.

Spellbook of the Master Descrição: If you control a Spellcaster-Type monster: You can reveal 1 other "Spellbook" card in your hand to target 1 "Spellbook" Normal Spell Card in your Graveyard, except "Spellbook of the Master"; this card's effect becomes that target's effect. You can only activate 1 "Spellbook of the Master" per turn.

Destiny Draw Descrição: Discard 1 "Destiny HERO" card; draw 2 cards.

Sage's Stone Descrição: If you control a face-up "Dark Magician Girl": Special Summon 1 "Dark Magician" from your hand or Deck.

Exchange Descrição: Both players reveal their hands and add 1 card from each other's hand to their hand.

Card Destruction Descrição: Each player discards their entire hand, then draws the same number of cards they discarded.

Foolish Burial Descrição: Send 1 Monster Card from your Deck to the Graveyard.

Dark World Lightning Descrição: Target 1 face-down card on the field; destroy that target, then discard 1 card.

Dark World Dealings Descrição: Each player draws 1 card, then each player discards 1 card.

Last Will Descrição: If a monster on your side of the field was sent to your Graveyard this turn, you can Special Summon 1 monster with an ATK of 1500 points or less from your Deck once during this turn. Then shuffle your Deck.

Mystic Box Descrição: Target 1 monster your opponent controls and 1 monster you control; destroy the first target, then give control of the second target to your opponent.

Toon Table of Contents Descrição: Add 1 "Toon" card or "Manga Ryu-Ran" from your Deck to your hand.

Double Summon Descrição: You can Normal Summon 1 additional time this turn. You can only gain this effect once per turn.

Thousand Knives Descrição: If you control a face-up "Dark Magician": Target 1 monster your opponent controls; destroy that target.

Parallel World Fusion Descrição: Choose an "Elemental HERO" Fusion Monster in your Extra Deck whose listed Fusion Material Monsters are banished, shuffle the banished Fusion Material Monsters into the Deck, then Special Summon that Fusion Monster from your Extra Deck. (This Special Summon is treated as a Fusion Summon.) You cannot Special Summon another monster(s) during the turn you activate this card.

Ookazi Descrição: Inflict 800 damage to your opponent.

Nightmare's Steelcage Descrição: This card remains face-up on the field for 2 of your opponent's turns. No monsters can attack. Destroy this card during your opponent's 2nd End Phase after this card was activated.

Lightning Vortex Descrição: Discard 1 card. Destroy all face-up monsters your opponent controls.

Giant Trunade Descrição: Return all Spell and Trap Cards on the field to their owners' hands.

Dark Hole Descrição: Destroy all monsters on the field.

Dark Factory of Mass Production Descrição: Target 2 Normal Monsters in your Graveyard; add those targets to your hand.

Confiscation Descrição: Pay 1000 Life Points. Look at your opponent's hand, select 1 card in it and discard that card.

Bonding - H2O Descrição: Tribute 2 "Hydrogeddons" and 1 "Oxygeddon". Special Summon 1 "Water Dragon" from your hand, Deck or Graveyard.

Block Attack Descrição: Select 1 face-up Attack Position monster on your opponent's side of the field and change it to Defense Position.

The Warrior Returning Alive Descrição: Target 1 Warrior-Type monster in your Graveyard; add that target to your hand.

Silent Doom Descrição: Special Summon 1 Normal Monster from your Graveyard in face-up Defense Position. It cannot attack.

Philosopher's Stone - Sabatiel Descrição: When a "Winged Kuriboh" on your side of the field is destroyed, you can add this card from your Deck to your hand. Pay half of your Life Points to add 1 card from your Deck or Graveyard to your hand. After this card is activated, it is placed into the Deck. Then shuffle the Deck. After you use this effect 3 times, this card takes on the following effect. Select 1 face-up monster on your side of the field and multiply its ATK by the number of monsters on your opponent's side of the field until this turn's End Phase.

Monster Reincarnation Descrição: Discard 1 card, then target 1 monster in your Graveyard; add it to your hand.

Graceful Charity Descrição: Draw 3 cards, then discard 2 cards.

Fusion Sage Descrição: Add 1 "Polymerization" card from your Deck to your hand. Then shuffle your Deck.

Fusion Recovery Descrição: Target 1 "Polymerization", and 1 Fusion Material Monster that was used for a Fusion Summon, in your Graveyard; add them to your hand.

Feather Shot Descrição: Target 1 face-up "Elemental HERO Avian" you control; during this turn, that target can attack a number of times equal to the number of monsters you control when this card resolves, but cannot attack directly, and other monsters you control cannot attack this turn.

Polymerization Descrição: Send, from your hand or your side of the field to the Graveyard, the Fusion Material Monsters that are listed on a Fusion Monster Card, then Special Summon that monster from your Extra Deck.

Tribute to the Doomed Descrição: Discard 1 card to target 1 monster on the field; destroy it.

Swords of Revealing Light Descrição: Flip all monsters your opponent controls face-up. This card remains on the field for 3 of your opponent's turns. While this card is face-up on the field, monsters your opponent controls cannot declare an attack.

Stop Defense Descrição:Select 1 Defense Position monster on your opponent's side of the field and change it to Attack Position.

Stamping Destruction Descrição: Activate only if you control a face-up Dragon-Type monster. Select 1 Spell or Trap Card on the field, destroy it and inflict 500 damage to its controller.

Soul Release Descrição: Select up to 5 cards from the Graveyard(s) and remove them from play.

Soul Exchange Descrição: Target 1 monster your opponent controls; this turn, if you Tribute a monster, you must Tribute that monster, as if you controlled it. You cannot conduct your Battle Phase the turn you activate this card.

Metamorphosis Descrição: Tribute 1 monster. Special Summon 1 Fusion Monster from your Fusion Deck with the same Level as the Tributed monster.

Hammer Shot Descrição: Destroy 1 face-up Attack Position monster with the highest ATK. (If it is a tie, you get to choose.)

Hieroglyph Lithograph Descrição: Pay 1000 Life Points. During the current Duel, your hand size limit becomes 7.

Mesmeric Control Descrição: During your opponent's next turn after you activate this card, your opponent cannot change the battle positions of monsters, except with a card effect.

Fissure Descrição: Destroy the 1 face-up monster your opponent controls that has the lowest ATK. (If it's a tie, you get to choose.)

Gold Sarcophagus Descrição: Banish 1 card from your Deck, face-up. During your second Standby Phase after this card's activation, add that card to your hand.

Elegant Egotist Descrição: Activate only while there is a face-up "Harpie Lady" on the field. Special Summon 1 "Harpie Lady" or "Harpie Lady Sisters" from your hand or your Deck.

Different Dimension Capsule Descrição: Select 1 card from Deck and remove it from play face-down. During your 2nd Standby Phase after activation, destroy this card and add the removed card to your hand.

Cost Down Descrição: Discard 1 card. Reduce the Level of all Monster Cards in your hand by 2 until the End Phase of this turn.

Change of Heart Descrição: Target 1 monster your opponent controls; take control of it until the End Phase.

Makiu, the Magical Mist Descrição: Target 1 face-up "Summoned Skull" or face-up Thunder-Type monster you control; destroy all monsters your opponent controls with DEF less than or equal to the ATK of that monster. You cannot conduct your Battle Phase the turn you activate this card.

De-Spell Descrição: Select 1 Spell Card on the field and destroy it. If the selected card is Set, pick up and see the card. If it is a Spell Card, it is destroyed. If it is a Trap Card, return it to its original position.

Ancient Rules Descrição: Special Summon 1 Level 5 or higher Normal Monster from your hand.

The Flute of Summoning Dragon Descrição: Special Summon up to 2 Dragon-Type monsters from your hand. There must be a face-up "Lord of D." on the field to activate and to resolve this effect.

E - Emergency Call Descrição: Add 1 "Elemental HERO" monster from your Deck to your hand.

R - Righteous Justice Descrição: Destroy Spell/Trap Cards equal to the number of face-up "Elemental HERO" cards you control.

O - Oversoul Descrição: Target 1 "Elemental HERO" Normal Monster in your Graveyard; Special Summon that target.

Heavy Storm Descrição: Destroy all Spell and Trap Cards on the field.

Pot of Greed Descrição: Draw 2 cards.

Monster Reborn Descrição: Target 1 monster in either player's Graveyard; Special Summon it.

Polymerization Descrição: Send, from your hand or your side of the field to the Graveyard, the Fusion Material Monsters that are listed on a Fusion Monster Card, then Special Summon that monster from your Extra Deck.

Shield & Sword Descrição: Switch the original ATK and DEF of all face-up monsters on the field until the end of this turn. Any additions and subtractions to ATK and DEF due to card effects are applied to the new ATK and DEF. Monsters Summoned after this card's activation are excluded.

Brain Control Descrição: Pay 800 Life Points to target 1 face-up monster your opponent controls; take control of that target until the End Phase.

Copy and WIN : http://bit.ly/copy_win