Xyz Effect Descrição: When you Xyz Summon a monster: You can target 1 card on the field; destroy it.

Curse Transfer (HQ) Descrição: Activate only when your opponent activates a Trap Card. Negate its effect and activate this card's effect as the negated effect.

D - Boost (HQ) Descrição: Activate only while "D - Force" is face-up on top of your Deck. Draw 2 cards from underneath "D - Force".

Shadow Balance (HQ) Descrição: Activate only when your opponent Summons a monster(s), and controls more monsters than you. Destroy monsters your opponent controls until both you and your opponent control the same number of monsters.

Disgraceful Charity (HQ) Descrição: Both players add all cards from their Graveyards that were discarded by the effect of a Spell Card activated this turn to their hands.

Dormant Volcano (HQ) Descrição: When this card is destroyed by a card effect and sent to the Graveyard, inflict 300 damage to your opponent. Then, during your next Standby Phase, both players can add 1 FIRE monster from their Decks to their hands.

Roll Out! Descrição: Target 1 Union monster in your Graveyard; equip that target to an appropriate monster you control.

Chronomaly Ley Line Power (HQ) Descrição: During the Battle Phase, when a monster Special Summoned during that Battle Phase battles another monster: Switch the battling monsters' ATK during the Damage Step only.

Vow of Tribe (HQ) Descrição: If both players each control a face-up monster with the same name as each other, those monsters cannot attack this turn.

 Eye of Ujat (HQ) Descrição: Activate only when your opponent declares an attack. Change the attack target to a monster your opponent controls, except the attacking monster.

Zero Gravity Descrição: Change the battle positions of all face-up monsters on the field.

Burst Breath Descrição: Tribute 1 Dragon-Type monster and destroy all face-up monsters on the field whose DEF is less than or equal to the Tributed monster's ATK.

Aquamirror Meditation Descrição: Reveal 1 Ritual Spell Card in your hand to target 2 "Gishki" monsters in your Graveyard; return them to the hand.

Aquamirror Illusion Descrição: Special Summon 1 "Gishki" Ritual Monster from your hand. It cannot attack, and is returned to the hand during the End Phase.

DNA Checkup Descrição: Select 1 face-down monster you control. Your opponent declares 2 Attributes. Reveal the selected monster. If its Attribute is one of the declared Attributes, your opponent draws 2 cards. If not, you draw 2 cards.

Double Magical Arm Bind (HQ) Descrição: Tribute 2 monsters and select 2 monsters your opponent controls. Take control of the selected monsters. Those monsters cannot attack or change their battle positions.

Harpie Lady Sparrow Formation (HQ) Descrição: Activate only when your opponent declares an attack while you control 2 or more face-up "Harpie Lady". Negate the attack and end the Battle Phase.

Rope of Life Descrição: When a monster(s) is destroyed by battle and sent to your Graveyard: Discard your entire hand (min.1), then target 1 of those monsters; Special Summon it, and if you do, it gains 800 ATK.

Zombie's Jewel (HQ) Descrição: Activate only when a card is sent to your opponent's Graveyard. Add that card to your hand. Your opponent draws 1 card.

Eye of Wdjat Descrição: Activated when an opponent's monster attacks. Take control of the selected monster until the End Phase of the turn this card is activated.

Chasm of Spikes Descrição: When an opponent's monster attacks, it is destroyed. The opponent loses Life Points equal to 1/4 of the monster's ATK.

Raging Sacred Curse Descrição: Activate only if you control a face-up Divine-Beast-Type monster, by selecting 1 face-up monster your opponent controls. Until the End Phase, that monster loses 2000 ATK and DEF, and is unaffected by the effects of your opponent's Spell and Trap Cards.

Descending Lost Star Descrição: Select 1 Synchro Monster in your Graveyard and Special Summon it in face-up Defense Position. Its effect is negated, its Level is reduced by 1 and its DEF becomes 0. Its battle position cannot be changed.

Meteor Stream Descrição: Activate only when a monster is Special Summoned during the turn it was sent from the field to the Graveyard as a Tribute. Inflict 1000 damage to your opponent.

Tuner's Mind Descrição: Activate only when a Synchro Monster you control is selected as an attack target. Return it to the Extra Deck. Then, if all the Synchro Material Monsters used in that monster's Synchro Summon are in your Graveyard, you can Special Summon them. If you do, the Tuner monster Special Summoned by this effect becomes the new attack target.

Shooting Star Descrição: Activate only if you control a face-up "Stardust Dragon". Select and destroy 1 card your opponent controls.

Different Dimension Ground Descrição: This turn, any monster sent to the Graveyard is removed from play instead.

Crevice Into the Different Dimension Descrição: Declare 1 Attribute and select a total of 2 monsters with that Attribute from either Graveyard. Remove those monsters from play.

White Hole Descrição: Activate only when your opponent activates "Dark Hole". The monsters you control are not destroyed.

Spell Reclamation Descrição: Discard 1 card and chain this card to a Spell Card you activated. Whenever that Spell Card is sent to the Graveyard, return it to its owner's hand.

Offering to the Snake Deity Descrição: Target 1 face-up Reptile-Type monster you control and 2 cards your opponent controls; destroy all three targets.

Dimensional Prison Descrição: When an opponent's monster declares an attack: Target that monster; banish that target.

D.D. Dynamite Descrição: Inflict 300 damage to your opponent for each of their removed from play cards.

Stonehenge Methods Descrição: When an "Chronomaly" monster you control is destroyed: Special Summon 1 Level 4 Rock-Type "Chronomaly" monster from your Deck in face-up Defense Position. It cannot change its battle position

Level Conversion Lab Descrição: Select 1 monster in your hand and show it to your opponent, then roll a six-sided die. If the result is 1, send the selected monster to the Graveyard. If the result is 2-6, the Level of the selected monster becomes equal to the result until the end of this turn.

Pyro Clock of Destiny Descrição: Move the turn count forward by 1 turn. The turn in which this card is activated continues as normal.

Infinity Force Descrição: Activate only if you control a face-up "Meklord Emperor" monster when your opponent activates a card effect that would inflict effect damage to you. Reduce that damage to 0, and destroy all monsters your opponent controls.

Inherited Fortune Descrição: Activate during the turn a face-up "Fortune Lady" monster you control was destroyed. Special Summon up to 2 "Fortune Lady" monsters from your hand during your next Standby Phase.

Meklord Emperor Creation Descrição: Send 1 "Sky Core", "Wise Core", and "Grand Core" from your hand to the Graveyard. Special Summon 1 "Meklord Astro Mekanikle" from your hand, Deck, or Graveyard.

Meklord Factory Descrição: Activate only when a face-up "Meklord" monster on the field is selected as an attack target. Select 1 "Meklord Army" monster in your Graveyard, and add it to your hand. Then, destroy the attack target.

Gagagarush Descrição: When a face-up "Gagaga" monster(s) you control is targeted by the effect of an opponent's monster: Negate the effect of that opponent's monster, and if you do, destroy it, then inflict damage to your opponent equal to the destroyed monster's ATK or DEF in the Graveyard (whichever is higher).

Gagagaguard Descrição: If you control 2 or more "Gagaga" monsters: During this turn, "Gagaga" monsters cannot be destroyed by battle.

TGX3-DX2 Descrição: Select 3 "T.G." monsters in your Graveyard. Return them to your Deck, then draw 2 cards.

TG-SX1 Descrição: Activate only when a "T.G." monster you control destroys an opponent's monster by battle and sends it to the Graveyard. Select 1 "T.G." Synchro Monster in your Graveyard and Special Summon it.

TG1-EM1 Descrição: Select 1 monster your opponent controls and 1 face-up "T.G." monster you control. Switch control of the selected monsters.

Traptrix Trap Hole Nightmare Descrição: When a monster your opponent controls that was Special Summoned this turn activates its effect: Negate that effect, and if you do, destroy that card.

Blackwing - Boobytrap Descrição: If this Set card is destroyed by a card effect, draw 1 card. Also, if you control a "Blackwing" monster, inflict 1000 damage to your opponent.

Blackboost Descrição: Activate only while you control 2 or more "Blackwing" monsters. Draw 2 cards.

Blackback Descrição: Select 1 "Blackwing" monster with 2000 or less ATK in your Graveyard, and Special Summon it. You cannot Normal Summon or Set monsters the turn you activate this card.

Black Thunder Descrição: Activate only when a "Blackwing" monster you control is destroyed by battle and sent to the Graveyard. Inflict 400 damage to your opponent for each card your opponent controls.

Black Return Descrição: Activate only when exactly 1 "Blackwing" monster is Special Summoned, by selecting 1 face-up monster your opponent controls. Gain Life Points equal to the ATK of that monster, then return it to the hand.

Black Feather Beacon Descrição: Activate only when you take damage from a battle or card effect. Special Summon 1 Level 4 or lower "Blackwing" monster from your hand or Deck.

Fake Feather Descrição: Send 1 "Blackwing" monster from your hand to the Graveyard and select 1 Normal Trap Card in your opponent's Graveyard. The effect of this card will be the same as the selected Normal Trap Card.

Delta Crow - Anti Reverse Descrição: Activate only while you control a face-up "Blackwing" monster. If you control at least 3 "Blackwing" monsters, this card can be activated from your hand. Destroy all face-down cards your opponent controls.

Tuner's Barrier Descrição: Select 1 face-up Tuner monster you control. That monster cannot be destroyed by battle or by card effects, until the End Phase of the next turn.

Synchro Strike Descrição: Target Synchro Summoned monster gains 500 ATK for each Synchro Material Monster used to Summon it, until the End Phase.

Synchro Material Descrição: During this turn, any monsters either player controls can be used as Synchro Material Monsters for a Synchro Summon.

Spirit Force Descrição: Activate only during damage calculation during your opponent's turn. You take no Battle Damage from that battle. Then, you can add 1 Warrior-Type Tuner monster with 1500 or less DEF from your Graveyard to your hand.

Slip Summon Descrição: Activate only when your opponent Summons a monster. Special Summon 1 Level 4 or lower monster from your hand in face-up Defense Position. Return it to the owner's hand during the End Phase.

Remote Revenge Descrição: Activate only by negating an opponent's card effect that would destroy a monster you control. Destroy all face-up Attack Position monsters your opponent controls.

Power Frame Descrição: When a face-up monster you control is targeted for an attack by a monster with a higher ATK: Target the attack target; negate that attack, and if you do, equip this card to that target. The equipped monster gains ATK equal to the difference between its ATK and the ATK of its attacker when this card resolves.

Miracle Locus Descrição: Select 1 face-up Attack Position monster you control. Your opponent draws 1 card. The selected monster gains 1000 ATK during the Damage Step and can attack twice this turn.

Dark Spirit Art - Greed Descrição: Tribute 1 DARK monster. Draw 2 cards. Your opponent can negate this effect by revealing 1 Spell Card in their hand.

Fake Life Descrição: When an opponent's monster declares a direct attack: Target that monster; negate the attack, and if you do, gain Life Points equal to its ATK.

Straight Flush Descrição: Activate only when all of your opponent's Spell & Trap Card Zones are occupied. Destroy all cards in your opponent's Spell & Trap Card Zones.

Defense Draw Descrição: Activate only during damage calculation during your opponent's turn. The Battle Damage you would receive becomes 0. Draw 1 card.

Nordic Relic Megingjord Descrição: Select 1 face-up "Aesir" or "Nordic" monster you control. Its ATK/DEF become double the original ATK/DEF, until the End Phase. That monster cannot attack your opponent directly this turn.

Nordic Relic Laevateinn Descrição: Select 1 face-up monster on the field that destroyed a monster by battle this turn. Destroy the selected monster. Cards and effects cannot be activated in response to this card.

Nordic Relic Gungnir Descrição: Remove from play 1 face-up "Aesir" or "Nordic" monster you control to select 1 card on the field. Destroy that card. During your 2nd End Phase after activation, the monster you removed to activate this card returns to the field in face-up Attack Position.

Nordic Relic Brisingamen Descrição: Select 1 face-up monster you control and 1 face-up monster your opponent controls on the field. The ATK of your monster becomes equal to the original ATK of selected monster; this change lasts until the End Phase. If your selected monster destroys an opponent's monster by battle and sends it to the Graveyard, inflict damage to your opponent equal to the ATK of the destroyed monster.

Gleipnir, the Fetters of Fenrir Descrição: Add 1 "Nordic" monster from your Deck to your hand.

Last Trick Descrição: If your opponent activates a Spell Card that would be sent to the Graveyard this turn, add that card to your hand instead.

Call of the Reaper Descrição: Activate only when a monster(s) is Special Summoned from your Graveyard. Select and Special Summon 1 "Supay" or 1 "Fire Ant Ascator" from your Graveyard.

Mask of Perplexity Descrição: Activate only when a monster you control is selected as an attack target. Your opponent selects 1 random monster on the field, except the attacking monster. Switch the target to that monster.

Morphtronics, Scramble! Descrição: Activate only when your opponent declares a direct attack while you control no monsters. Negate the attack and Special Summon 1 "Morphtronic" monster from your hand.

Morphtronic Mix-up Descrição: If you control 2 or more face-up "Morphtronic" monsters, select 2 cards your opponent controls. Destroy 1 card of your opponent's choice from those 2.

Morphtransition Descrição: Activate only when a face-up "Morphtronic" monster you control is selected as an attack target. Negate the attack, and change the battle position of the selected "Morphtronic" monster.

Synchro Spirits Descrição: Select 1 Synchro Monster from your Graveyard and remove it from play. If all of the monsters that were used for the Synchro Summon of that monster are in your Graveyard, you can Special Summon them to your side of the field.

Synchro Back Descrição: Return 1 Synchro Monster you control to the Extra Deck. Special Summon it during your next Standby Phase.

Revival Gift Descrição: Select 1 Tuner monster from your Graveyard and Special Summon it. Its effects are negated. Special Summon 2 "Gift Fiend Tokens" (Fiend-Type/DARK/Level 3/ATK 1500/DEF 1500) to your opponent's side of the field.

Phantom Destruction Descrição: Select 1 face-up card on the field. Flip it face-down.

Nature's Reflection Descrição: During this turn, any effect activated by your opponent that would inflict damage becomes an effect that inflicts damage to their Life Points.

Shockwave Descrição: Activate only while your Life Points are lower than your opponent's. Select 1 monster on the field, and destroy it. Then, inflict damage to both players equal to its ATK.

Return of the Six Samurai Descrição: Target 1 "Six Samurai" monster in your Graveyard; Special Summon that target. Destroy it during the End Phase of this turn.

Urgent Tuning Descrição: Activate only during the Battle Phase. Synchro Summon 1 Synchro Monster. (Send the appropriate Synchro Material Monsters to the Graveyard.)

Chain Whirlwind Descrição: Activate only when a card on the field is destroyed by a card effect. Select 2 Spell/Trap Cards on the field and destroy

Chain Healing Descrição: Gain 500 Life Points. If this card was activated as Chain Link 2 or 3, add this card to the Deck and shuffle it. If this card was activated as Chain Link 4 or higher, return this card to the hand.

Chain Disappearance Descrição: When a monster(s) with 1000 or less ATK is Summoned: Banish that monster(s) with 1000 or less ATK, then your opponent banishes all cards with the same name as that card(s) from their hand and Deck.

Chain Detonation Descrição: Inflict 500 damage to your opponent. If this card was activated as Chain Link 2 or 3, add this card to the Deck and shuffle it. If this card was activated as Chain Link 4 or higher, return this card to the hand.

Blast with Chain Descrição: Target 1 face-up monster you control; equip this card to that target. It gains 500 ATK. When this card is destroyed by a card effect while equipped: Target 1 card on the field; destroy that target.

Karakuri Trick House Descrição: Activate only when the battle position of a face-up "Karakuri" monster you control is changed. Select 1 card on the field, and destroy it.

Karakuri Klock Descrição: Activate only when a face-up Defense Position "Karakuri" monster is selected as an attack target. Destroy all face-up monsters your opponent controls.

Parasite Worm Descrição: Activate only when your opponent Summons a monster. Destroy it and inflict damage to your opponent equal to its ATK.

Convert Ghost Descrição: Activate only when a monster you control is targeted by a card effect. Change the target to a monster in your Graveyard. In that case, that monster is treated as a face-up monster you control, without counting toward your 5 Monster Card Zone limit. Then, Set this card face-down again instead of sending it to the Graveyard.

For Our Dreams Descrição: Tribute 1 Warrior-Type monster you control to select 1 face-up Warrior-Type monster you control. It cannot be destroyed by battle while face-up on the field.

Null and Void Descrição: Activate only when your opponent draws a card from his/her Deck, or plays a card from his/her hand. That card is negated and sent to the Graveyard.

Thunder of Ruler Descrição: During your opponent's Standby Phase: You can activate this card; there is no Battle Phase this turn.

Threatening Roar Descrição: Your opponent cannot declare an attack this turn.

Secret Barrel Descrição: Inflict 200 damage to your opponent for each card in their hand and for each card on their side of the field.

Ojama Trio Descrição: Special Summon 3 "Ojama Tokens" (Beast-Type/LIGHT/Level 2/ATK 0/DEF 1000) in Defense Position on your opponent's side of the field. The tokens cannot be Tributed for a Tribute Summon. When an "Ojama Token" is destroyed, the controller of that token takes 300 points of damage.

Dimension Wall Descrição: Activate only when an opponent's monster declares an attack. Instead of you, your opponent takes the Battle Damage you would have taken from this battle.

Compulsory Evacuation Device Descrição: Target 1 monster on the field; return that target to the hand.

Cocoon Veil Descrição: Activate by Tributing 1 face-up "Chrysalis" monster. This turn, any damage to you caused by an effect becomes 0. Special Summon 1 "Neo-Spacian" monster written on the "Chrysalis" monster you Tributed, from your hand, Deck or from either player's Graveyard.

Backup Soldier Descrição: Activate only if there are 5 or more monsters in your Graveyard. Add up to 3 non-Effect Monsters with 1500 ATK or less from your Graveyard to your hand.

Really Eternal Rest Descrição: Destroy all monsters equipped with an Equip Card(s).

Collected Power Descrição: Target 1 face-up monster on the field; equip it with all Equip Cards on the field. If any of those Equip Cards is now equipped to an incorrect target, destroy that Equip Card.

Judgment of the Pharaoh Descrição: Pay half your Life Points. Select and activate an appropriate effect which can be applied: ● If "Yu-Jo Friendship" is in your Graveyard, until the end of this turn: your opponent cannot Normal Summon, Set, Flip Summon, or Special Summon a monster(s), or activate an Effect Monster's effect, and their monsters' effects are negated. ● If "Unity" is in your Graveyard, until the end of this turn: negate the effects of all Spell and Trap Cards on your opponent's side of the field, and your opponent cannot activate or Set Spell or Trap Cards.

Time Seal Descrição: Skip the Draw Phase of your opponent's next turn.

Covering Fire Descrição: If your opponent's monster attacks a monster on your side of the field, you can activate this card during the Damage Step. Your attacked monster gains ATK equal to the ATK of 1 other face-up monster on your side of the field during the Damage Step only.

Reversal of Fate Descrição: All "Arcana Force" monsters on the field have their respective effects now treated as the opposite coin toss result.

Arcana Call Descrição: Select 1 "Arcana Force" monster you control. Remove from play 1 "Arcana Force" monster from either player's Graveyard. Until the End Phase, the selected monster's effect gains the removed monster's effect for the same coin toss result.

Chthonian Polymer Descrição: You can only activate this card when your opponent Fusion Summons a Fusion Monster. Tribute 1 monster on your side of the field to take control of that Fusion Monster.

Zero Hole (5D's) Descrição: Activate only while you have no cards in your hand. Destroy all cards on the field.

Life Shaver Descrição: Your opponent must discard 1 card from their hand for each of your turns that this card has been Set.

Dragon's Rebirth Descrição: Target 1 face-up Dragon-Type monster you control; banish that target and Special Summon 1 Dragon-Type monster from your hand or Graveyard.

Fragment Fusion Descrição: Banish from your Graveyard, the Fusion Material Monsters that are listed on a "Gem-Knight" Fusion Monster Card, then Special Summon that Fusion Monster from your Extra Deck. (This Special Summon is treated as a Fusion Summon.) Destroy it during the End Phase.

Gem-Enhancement Descrição: Tribute 1 "Gem-Knight" monster, then target 1 "Gem-Knight" monster in your Graveyard; Special Summon that target from the Graveyard.

Acid Trap Hole Descrição: Target 1 face-down Defense Position monster on the field; flip it face-up, then destroy it if its DEF is 2000 or less, or return it face-down if its DEF is more than 2000.

Venom Burn Descrição: Select 1 monster with a Venom Counter(s). Remove all Venom Counters from that card, and inflict 700 damage to your opponent for each Venom Counter removed.

Scrap-Iron Scarecrow (OCG) Descrição: When an opponent's monster declares an attack: Target the attacking monster; negate that target's attack, then Set this card face-down again instead of sending it to the Graveyard.

Dramatic Rescue Descrição: Activate only when a card is activated that targets a monster. Return the targeted monster to its owner's hand and Special Summon 1 other monster from your hand.

Dramatic Rescue (OCG) Descrição: Activate only when a card is activated that targets a monster. Return the targeted monster to its owner's hand and Special Summon 1 other monster from your hand.

Arsenal Robber Descrição: Your opponent selects 1 Equip Spell Card from his/her Deck and sends it to the Graveyard.

Fiend Comedian (OCG) Descrição: Toss a coin and call it. If you call it right, all of your opponent's cards in the Graveyard are removed from play immediately. If you call it wrong, send a number of cards equal to the number of cards in your opponent's Graveyard from your Deck to your Graveyard.

Dramatic Crossroads Descrição: Activate only when you take Battle Damage. Your opponent selects and activates 1 of these effects: * Discard 1 random card. * Your opponent looks at your hand, selects 1 card in it, and adds it to their hand.

Fake Trap Descrição: Activate only when your opponent activates a Spell Card, Trap Card, or Effect Monster that destroys one or more Trap Cards you control. Reveal the cards would be destroyed by your opponent, and only destroy this card instead.

Dark Mirror Force Descrição: When an opponent's monster declares an attack: Banish all Defense Position monsters your opponent controls.

Cemetary Bomb Descrição: Inflict 100 damage to your opponent for each card in their Graveyard.

D. Tribe Descrição: All monsters on your side of the field are treated as Dragon-Type until the End Phase of this turn.

Infernity Break Descrição: Activate only if you have no cards in your hand. Select 1 "Infernity" card in your Graveyard and remove it from play. Select 1 card your opponent controls and destroy it.

Infernity Force Descrição: Activate only when an "Infernity" monster is selected as an attack target while you have no cards in your hand. Destroy the attacking monster and Special Summon 1 Level 4 or lower "Infernity" monster from your Graveyard.

Infernity Inferno Descrição: Discard up to 2 cards and send the same number of "Infernity" cards from your Deck to the Graveyard.

Infernity Reflector Descrição: Activate only by discarding all the cards in your hand when an "Infernity" monster is destroyed by battle and sent to the Graveyard. Select and Special Summon that monster from your Graveyard and inflict 1000 damage to your opponent.

Legacy of Yata-Garasu Descrição: Activate 1 of these effects: ● Draw 1 card. ● Activate only if your opponent controls a face-up Spirit monster. Draw 2 cards.

Dark Scorpion Combination Descrição: You can only activate this card when there are "Don Zaloog", "Cliff the Trap Remover", "Dark Scorpion - Chick the Yellow", "Dark Scorpion - Gorg the Strong", and "Dark Scorpion - Meanae the Thorn" face-up on your side of the field. During this turn, any of these 5 cards can attack your opponent's Life Points directly. In that case, the Battle Damage inflicted to your opponent by each of those cards becomes 400 points.

Dark Scorpion Retreat Descrição: Activate only while you control a face-up "Don Zaloog", "Cliff the Trap Remover", "Dark Scorpion - Chick the Yellow", "Dark Scorpion - Gorg the Strong" and "Dark Scorpion - Meanae the Thorn". Return them to your hand.

Revival of the Immortals Descrição: Select 1 "Earthbound Immortal" monster in your Graveyard. Special Summon that monster. It cannot declare an attack this turn. Whenever it battles, your opponent takes no Battle Damage.

Contaminated Earth Descrição: When 1 Level 8 or higher monster and 1 or more other monsters you control are destroyed and sent to the Graveyard: Special Summon 1 "Earthbound Immortal" monster from your hand, Deck, or Graveyard. This turn, that monster cannot attack or activate its effects.

Earthbound Release Descrição: Activate only when a Level 6 or higher monster is Normal or Special Summoned to your opponent's side of the field. Tribute 1 "Earthbound Immortal" monster. Destroy all monsters your opponent controls, and inflict damage to your opponent equal to the total ATK of the destroyed monsters.

Offering to the Immortals Descrição: Activate only when your opponent's monster declares a direct attack. Negate the attack. Afterwards, you can Special Summon 2 "Ceremonial Tokens" (Rock-Type/EARTH/Level 1/ATK 0/DEF 0) and/or add 1 "Earthbound Immortal" card from your Deck to your hand.

Fairy's Hand Mirror Descrição: Switch the opponent's Spell Card effect that specifically designates 1 monster as a target to another correct target.

Crystal Raigeki Descrição: Send 1 "Crystal Beast" card from your Spell & Trap Card Zone to the Graveyard to target 1 card your opponent controls; destroy that target.

Solar Ray Descrição: Inflict 600 points of damage to your opponent's Life Points for each face-up LIGHT monster on your side of the field.

Reckless Greed Descrição: Draw 2 cards and skip your next 2 Draw Phases

Michizure Descrição: Activate only when a monster is sent from the field to your Graveyard. Select and destroy 1 monster on the field. (You can activate this card during the Damage Step.)

Dark Spirit of the Silent Descrição: Activate only when an opponent's monster declares an attack. Negate that attack, and select another face-up monster your opponent controls. That monster attacks instead. (If it is in face-up Defense Position, change it to Attack Position.)

Bottomless Trap Hole Descrição: When your opponent Summons a monster(s) with 1500 or more ATK: Destroy that monster(s) with 1500 or more ATK, and if you do, banish it instead of sending it to the Graveyard.

Castle Walls Descrição: Increase the DEF of 1 face-up monster on the field by 500 points until the end of this turn.

Exchange of the Spirit Descrição: Activate only while there are 15 or more cards in your Graveyard. Pay 1000 Life Points. Both players swap the card(s) in their Graveyard with the card(s) in their Deck. Then, both players shuffle their Deck.

Curse of Anubis Descrição: All face-up Effect Monsters on the field are changed to Defense Position. During the turn this card is activated, the original DEF of those Effect Monsters become 0 and their battle positions cannot be changed, except with a card effect.

Gift Card Descrição: Your opponent gains 3000 Life Points.

Mask of Weakness Descrição: Select 1 attacking monster. It loses 700 ATK until the End Phase.

Jar of Greed Descrição: Draw 1 card from your Deck.

Hidden Spellbook Descrição: During your turn: Target 2 Spell Cards in your Graveyard; shuffle those targets into the Deck.

Amazoness Shamanism Descrição: Destroy all face-up "Amazoness" monsters you control. Then, you can Special Summon any number of Level 4 or lower "Amazoness" monsters from your Graveyard in face-up Defense Position, up to the number of monsters destroyed by this effect.

D - Chain Descrição: Target a "Destiny HERO" monster you control; equip this card to that target. It gains 500 ATK. When it destroys a monster your opponent controls by battle and sends it to the Graveyard: Inflict 500 damage to your opponent.

Eternal Dread Descrição: Put 2 Clock Counters on "Clock Tower Prison".

Dust Tornado Descrição: Target 1 Spell/Trap Card your opponent controls; destroy that target, then you can Set 1 Spell/Trap Card from your hand.

Chain Destruction Descrição: When a monster(s) with 2000 or less ATK is Summoned: Target 1 of them; destroy all cards with that name in its controller's hand and Deck.

Skull Dice Descrição: Roll 1 six-sided die. The face-up monsters your opponent currently controls lose ATK and DEF equal to the result x 100, until the End Phase.

Graverobber Descrição: Select 1 Spell Card from your opponent's Graveyard. You can use it as your hand until the end of the turn. If you use it, you take 2000 points of damage.

Gorgon's Eye Descrição: Until the end of this turn, all effects of Defense Position monsters are negated.

Torrential Tribute Descrição: When a monster(s) is Summoned: Destroy all monsters on the field.

Shift Descrição: When your opponent targets exactly 1 monster you control for an attack, or with a Spell/Trap effect: Target another monster you control that would be an appropriate target; that attack/Spell/Trap now targets the new target.

Magician's Circle Descrição: When a Spellcaster-Type monster declares an attack: Each player Special Summons 1 Spellcaster-Type monster with 2000 or less ATK from their Deck in face-up Attack Position.

Kunai with Chain Descrição: Activate 1 or both of these effects (simultaneously). ● When an opponent's monster attacks: Target the attacking monster; change that target to Defense Position. ● Target 1 face-up monster you control; equip this card to that target. It gains 500 ATK.

Lightforce Sword Descrição: Select 1 random card from your opponent's hand and remove it from play face-down. During your opponent's 4th Standby Phase after this card's activation, return that card to their hand.

Magical Hats Descrição: During your opponent's Battle Phase: Choose 2 non-Monster Cards from your Deck and 1 monster you control. Shuffle those 3 cards and Set them on the field in Defense Position. The 2 cards chosen from your Deck are treated as Normal Monsters (ATK 0/DEF 0) and are destroyed at the end of the Battle Phase.

Reinforcements Descrição: Target monster gains 500 ATK until the end of this turn.

Enchanted Javelin Descrição: Increase your Life Points by the ATK of 1 attacking monster.

Mirror Gate Descrição: When an opponent's monster declares an attack targeting a face-up "Elemental HERO" monster you control: Switch control of the opponent's attacking monster with the targeted monster you control, then calculate damage. Control of both monsters switches back during the End Phase

Hero Barrier Descrição: Negate 1 attack from an opponent's monster. You must control a face-up "Elemental HERO" monster to resolve this effect.

Hero Ring Descrição: Target 1 Warrior-Type monster with an 1500 or less ATK; equip this card to that target. Monsters your opponent controls with 1900 or more ATK cannot attack that target.

Final Fusion Descrição: Activate only when a face-up Fusion Monster you control battles an opponent's Fusion Monster. Each player takes damage equal to the combined ATK of the battling monsters. You can activate this card during damage calculation.

Hero Signal Descrição: When a monster you control is destroyed by battle and sent to the Graveyard: Special Summon 1 Level 4 or lower "Elemental HERO" monster from your hand or Deck.

Trap Stun Descrição: Negate the effects of all other Trap Cards on the field during this turn.

Mirror Force Descrição: When an opponent's monster declares an attack: Destroy all Attack Position monsters your opponent controls.

Waboku Descrição: You take no Battle Damage this turn. Your monsters cannot be destroyed by battle this turn.

Sakuretsu Armor Descrição: When an opponent's monster declares an attack: Target the attacking monster; destroy that target.

Ring of Destruction Descrição: Target 1 face-up monster on the field; destroy that target, and if you do, inflict damage to both players equal to that target's ATK.

Crush Card Virus Descrição: Tribute 1 DARK monster with 1000 or less ATK. Check all monsters your opponent controls, your opponent's hand, and all cards they draw (until the end of your opponent's 3rd turn after this card's activation), and destroy all monsters with 1500 or more ATK.

Trap Hole Descrição: When your opponent Normal or Flip Summons 1 monster with 1000 or more ATK: Target that monster; destroy that target.

Magic Cylinder Descrição: When an opponent's monster declares an attack: Target the attacking monster; negate the attack, and if you do, inflict damage to your opponent equal to its ATK.

 Draining Shield Descrição: When an opponent's monster declares an attack: Target the attacking monster; negate that attack, and if you do, gain Life Points equal to that target's ATK.

Copy and WIN : http://bit.ly/copy_win